And we are live. Good morning, America.
What's up? What's up?
>> Yes. And good afternoon, Europe.
>> Yes.
Uh, how you doing, man? Like burning
token like crazy.
>> Yes. It was a late night because I had
to use all my tokens on Fable.
You should have like routines or slash
uh automations to burn token before
release day.
>> Yeah.
>> And I already was was lucky.
>> I was almost at 90% usage yesterday
evening and that's the moment when they
told we have reseted all the counters.
So I was like yes.
>> Yeah.
>> Because Fab is expensive.
>> Yes. Double expensive compared to Opus.
Yes sir.
But
>> is it double as good?
Um
I the benchmarks I saw. Okay. Okay.
Let's talk about that. Uh let me do the
demo first. Introduction demo.
>> Yes.
>> Okay.
Last week we built uh once a game in
with one prompt with Opus 4.8. eight.
Yesterday, Fable 5 launched and now
what? We are going to build a full AI
native gaming studios
>> with one prompt
>> with maybe two.
>> Maybe two.
>> So, if you want to see what's Fable 5 is
capable of, watch this video. Woo!
animation.
>> And the cool thing is
>> Fable already here makes you think of a
game, right?
>> I mean,
>> it's a perfect name.
>> I mean, for for sure. Like, for sure.
>> Game Studio AI.
>> Yes. Did Did you play Fable on Xbox when
it was launched ago?
>> No, I didn't. I think I did like once or
so, but I
>> I can't even remember. So, it's not too
good. It's a game like when you take
like decision uh it impact your
character. So if you go to the uh ail
side of it, you look like a demon at the
end of the game and stuff like that and
you are an angel if you are like a good
person or something.
>> So if you actually want to walk around,
you always have to do good because
otherwise people go after you.
>> Yeah, something like that. Yes. But
you're more powerful. So the game play
changed. That was a big game when it
like first
>> Yeah. Imagine what they could have done
if they had AI.
>> GTA 6, man.
>> Oh, yeah. Well,
>> let's have a game studio ready to make
everything possible.
>> Let's build GTS GTS 7 with something
rockar.
>> Yeah. And release it one month after.
>> Exactly. Like, let's be AI rock AI star
now. Or rockstar. How do you reverse
rockstar like a
rock? So, rap or hip-hop? No.
It doesn't matter. We make it better.
>> Whatever. So,
uh, t uh demo bam uh code path.
I changed that. Why is that not
persistent noise
tech? And I have that. That's perfect.
Cool.
Uh, yes. Uh,
a tweet from Clo. Introducing Yeah. I
mean, no [__] It's from Clo. It's
introducing Fable.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh, introducing Fable 5. A Mythos class
model that we have made safe for general
use. AK. They make it dumb and you can't
attack the Pagon with it.
>> Yes. And they make it sound like they
have a warship class.
>> Yeah.
It's capability exceed those of any
model we have ever made generally
available. And what everyone wants to do
is like if the the name if the numbers
are bigger than before and they are like
everywhere and that was big
>> and it's a big difference.
>> Yeah, that's massive.
>> It's getting more and more difficult to
get higher numbers because the higher
you get the harder it is to scale up.
Yeah,
>> because uh yeah, so that that's why they
create also new benchmark every Sunday
and all of a sudden like
>> yeah, okay, let's uh we have maxed out
benchmark. So let's let's make another
one.
Uh so aent coding yeah S swa benchmark
pro and frontier code diamond. Yeah, I
guess different providers but same
benchmark. Uh 5.5 XI was at 5.7%
on Agent Kenic like the Frontier Code.
31 on Xi Mitos/Fable 5. That's that's
nuts.
>> That's a big difference.
>> Yeah. I don't know what's the model is
or if they game it like you know because
they can basically train on it.
>> Mhm.
>> Uh yeah, it's way bigger than 5.5 and
5.5 is was good.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh you know 4.8 8 ultra code. When I go
back to 5.5, then I don't like the model
anymore.
>> No. What? It still feels like every
update does the same thing. Now I did
Meas. Oh, yeah. Fable.
>> And I feel like Opus is dumb.
>> Yeah, but I buy a lot. Yeah,
because I actually checked myself and
when Opus said that my system was good
to go and no bugs, I asked Fable and he
found like a full list.
>> Yes, that's And do you prefer to pay
more because we're going to talk about
the pricing like in a minute. Do you
prefer to pay more uh but have a better
output or have 70 80% of the job done
and then you need to come back and
verify everything a couple of time and
>> yeah I like to do it in steps still
because I don't think it can oneshot a
perfect system.
>> Yeah.
>> I think that that's they say they can do
it and it can work longer but then it
gets really expensive because it has
bigger memory. But I Yeah, true. But I
think it's because our specs are not
their specs.
>> Oh, yeah. For sure.
>> But our token burn is higher than
theirs.
>> And we don't have that money.
>> No. Yeah. So, the best option is for now
to just get an another subscription.
>> Yeah. I bro I I bought another one like
200 a month uh basically just for that
>> because we have 15 days and we're going
to talk about that too.
>> Yes.
>> Uh okay. So other than that the big jump
uh special reasoning that that could be
good like if they could push image video
model that would be fun to try.
uh blueprint uh multi multi-disiplinary
reasoning 59 from 56 56 and 41 from uh
GPT5. Yeah. So basically everywhere it's
numbers goes up.
>> Mhm.
>> Terminal benchmark 88 instead of 8.3 uh
8.2 on 4.8 on Yes. And cyber security
78. But basically, if you try to check
my network and uh find any issues, it's
got no no you're hacking now. So get
out.
>> And I tried it yesterday. I first said,
"Okay, please double check my login and
make sure it's not hackable."
>> And
it it said in yellow letters in my uh
terminal window. I switched to Opus
because of security.
>> Yeah, that's nuts. So it looks like when
you make the prompt too much on uh
trying to find options to hack that it
switches to opus and it doesn't give you
the full potential of fable.
>> But afterwards I said hey this is my
code please do a security check and it
just proceeded and did everything.
>> Okay. So you you use opus to go to pass
the security and then you go back to
>> no I just did different prompts but if
you in your prompt write down or at
least that was what I what I found out
then in your prompt you find something
that it uh you want to know if people
can hack this then it will just say hey
I'm not doing this I'm switching back to
the opus model and I wish you all the
best.
>> Okay. So I think that's one of their
securities that they put in to make sure
that people don't abuse it.
>> Yeah, that makes sense. But like can can
they really like uh catch all of the use
case or because yeah I saw on Twitter
like some uh feedback and they they said
yeah do some research about cancer like
can some blah blah blah like can can we
have some alternative cure for cancer
whatever and it blocked right away. So
>> yeah, because I was going to block on
security and biological uh stuff.
>> So you can build a nucleus. Uh
>> yeah,
>> but afterwards when I said I just want a
security check on this code, it checked
the entire login and it gave me like
three issues.
So that was just a different prompt
>> and maybe it understands the context of
the app too and it say like okay it's a
SAS/WordPress whatever and then yeah
that's interesting uh yeah okay so
pricing um okay yeah first
uh wait API uh 15 uh June
that's an important sentence where is it
uh yes from today through through June
June 22, Fable 5 is included on a Pro
Max team and seedbased enterprise plan
at no extra cost. On June 23rd, we will
remove Fable 5 from those plan using it
after that will require usage credits.
>> Yeah.
>> [__] off.
>> So even if you use it in your terminal
>> Yeah.
>> will it then also go to credits?
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. like we will not have it
on the subscriptionbased uh
>> yeah well this is something that we said
last time right when is the moment
>> that they are going to charge you so
much more and that you're addicted to
the AI and you can can't live without it
>> yeah but I'm not paying API press stuff
like that
how to get bankrupt yeah I just like
prompted uh Fable 5 and also like the um
the integrity of the output.
>> Mhm.
>> It's never like relable enough to Okay,
you bro, you spend 45 minutes uh
spinning off 70 agents. That happened to
me last night and the bug is still here.
So,
>> yeah. Yeah, but you spent like 2.5
million tokens.
>> Yeah, exactly. And uh I yesterday
because I reached my limit too like um
I turn out extra credit just to uh
finish some task and stuff. I burn 50
bucks just like that.
>> Yeah.
>> Like insane. Uh okay. And so we have
that and usage credit. Okay. And finally
the pricing. So
10 B uh $10 uh in and 50 out.
mess five. Okay. Same price. And for
Opus, yes, for Opus it was 525 and on
Sony it's 315
>> and one 125
>> and they doubled the cost for meters,
right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's it's like twice obvious
for meters.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's 10 to 50. Yeah.
>> Well, that goes hard. Especially if you
put it on ultra and you just leave and
you go
>> touching some grass outside and after an
hour you come back, you can have a bill
of $250
easy.
>> Yeah. Like like I max out two accounts
of five hours session limit by having
four five session of ultra code uh fable
five. Let's go, bro.
>> Yeah.
So yeah,
it's it's interesting but we have better
better output and uh okay so I wanted
that and oh okay so fable games now what
people are building and that's
definitely interesting is
that
uh 5 is insane. It were from the little
fantasy world mush. I don't think it's
true because how do you how do you
generate the assets from clothes?
>> I don't know. But this looks like World
of Warcraft or whatever
>> created by Tes. Yeah, it's a fake fake
>> uh an AI using a second prompt in the
video. The character moves smoothly and
what what mark is visible
entropic model rejection coding
capability likely contribute. Yeah, but
I mean you need to generate the asset
anyway, but uh yeah, that that looks
that
>> Yeah, but probably they have everything
already in it and they just switch to a
different model.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh,
>> so they have the entire setup, they have
the assets in it for generation, the
prompts,
>> instead of using Opus, they switch to
another one and they show that it's
looking better and and everything.
Uh, next I will create fable.
I mean, yeah, because
like what we at last week was like all
of the sprite for the game stuff that
the short FPS was react 3GS but the
default um uh not sprite but just like
geometry layer etc. Like you will see in
one of the game uh that I've prompted
after that it's just like geometry
figures. There is no image at all. So
yeah, it can copy but no base. Okay.
Okay.
Uh tech t tech tag I just designed a
website with fable. It launched today.
Honestly the line uh between AI
generated design and human design are
blowing fast. Yeah.
>> And Figma to actually provide
>> I want that. I want that.
Yeah. You can still see that. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, it it is looking good, but
on the other hand, if you create like 50
websites, I think at least 10 are
looking the exact same.
>> Yeah, exactly. Yeah, it's really hard to
have like some unique
>> but also it's because everyone is using
the same library like shen stuff. So,
yeah, if it's not fine tuning to what
you want.
>> No, you need to do that before you
start.
>> Yeah, exactly. I mean that looks
>> if this is the first things that you see
then this looks good and then you keep
on scrolling on X and you see other
people and you see the same uh layouts
the same images and everything
>> uh AI subscription are there the clothes
fable will only be an entropic
subscription until June 22 after that we
need to pay for usage per token for this
model will not be included in subs yeah
okay cloud fable Control extra high.
Make a Pokemon clone. One hour of
reasoning. 8K line. One shot. Uh,
really? Oh, maybe it can take the sprite
from like internet though cuz it's
probably everywhere.
Not perfect. Clanky text artifact blah
blah blah
including the music.
>> Yeah, because that Yeah, they can
generate studio music.
So that's that's okay. That's nice.
Yeah, you can get the sprite. Yeah.
Okay. So there's no attack and that's
Minecraft. Yeah. Same thing. All of
those sprites. I believe that because uh
it's everywhere on internet. So you can
download them for free since forever. So
yeah and this one quickly. So ask Fable
to make me another back rooms games like
>> code one
I won't that's
it. Yes he's using it
>> little MacBook I could run.
Okay dude the liinal noise. Okay it
actual playback. Dude that's nuts. What?
>> My MacBook I could run.
Okay, dude. The liinal noise. Okay, it
gener Okay, I didn't see anything,
>> you know. It still isn't doing anything,
but
>> yeah. Uh, tag Minecraft. Oh, yeah.
That's a Slenderman man stuff. Yeah.
Okay.
>> Mhm.
>> Big go play. Oh,
>> you can test it.
>> Yeah. Uh, I just don't want like
screaming stuff in my
Oh, they I'm afraid. I'm afraid.
Okay. I can't.
>> You can't delete.
>> Yeah. This is just waiting for that one
moment where in front of you.
The sound. Do you hear the sound?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Whoa.
>> Oh, that's cool.
Okay.
Uhuh. I don't like that.
>> It's never good to go into a oneway.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Into a dead end.
That works well.
Yeah. Yeah.
>> Or maybe there is nothing. It is just
attention of
>> uh uh
>> Oh, you found it.
>> Really?
>> That's it.
It's not working. Not working. I don't
want to go back.
Woo.
>> And never outside.
>> Oh, you're going down into the next
room.
>> That's nice. I won't.
>> That's nice. That works well.
>> Yeah. And now that was just the first
prompt, right? So, this is like the
basics and now you can continue.
>> That's what he said.
>> Oh, yeah. Amega cooked with a very
simple prompt. Okay, let me bring it
back.
back back. Yeah, it say five minutes
clip contain a quick walk through the
full prompt through game play. Okay.
I mean I mean also like it it didn't
create a new game type. It like bringing
like more uh like other sprite or the
type of game and generate. It didn't
like create same thing for like uh our
game stuff. It's just an FPS that looks
like Doom, right? So, it's different.
Uh okay. So, we have that. But
technically, again, technically it's
down.
>> Yeah.
>> And now I'm just curious how many people
are building it now and are going to
spend like millions of tokens daily
after two weeks.
>> Exactly. Uh but that's why like we need
a space compute.
>> Yeah.
>> 3D game strategy solo browser base no
install economy tech tree thanks a first
game realistically do three months alone
has 100 million play number. Let's find
out. Yeah pretty cool that looks like a
C five or something
posted. Okay cool cool it's kind of nuts
react entities I really apply scared.
Okay.
Nice. Okay. So now
uh
so from
from our little
uh stream from last week we did that. Uh
yes.
>> Yes. But this is cool. you.
>> Oh, hi. Reacting to our
>> what we have done yesterday last week
was that.
>> Yes.
>> But this is cool. You have actually a
working game already.
>> Nice video.
>> And uh yeah, we left it over with the
same uh pieces all together. We put like
we prompted like um uh a couple of times
after but now
>> you made some upgrades.
>> Yeah. Uh automatically. Okay. So the way
I did it was to um I got another account
and then I run it on automations.
>> Mhm.
>> Like every hours, two hours and four
hours because uh then it was taking too
much token. So I every four hours I had
a uh GitHub board with all of the
features and all of the direction that I
wanted. And now welcome to ship [__]
games.
>> Yeah. Just to tell people that you did
this with your own skills, your own
prompts.
>> Yeah.
>> And your own automation to to optimize
everything. It is not a oneshotted game.
>> Yeah. No. No. Exactly. Yeah. It's
basically like since last week uh auto
uh automations loop
>> and uh verification for the asset and
stuff. It's not like 100% done yet, but
it's getting there. So,
>> we have a website. We have 200 200
commits in 30 days. I also have a
built-in public uh git tracker know it's
connected to GitHub and it tracks all of
the commits.
>> Okay, that's cool.
>> I didn't build seven games. Uh, one game
per seven.
>> Mhm.
>> Uh, production sprites. Okay, that's
nice. Uh, like for the weapon and stuff
like that. Uh, Pierre ships 200 130
pier. Okay, so seven games. I'm going to
show you all of them uh after that. But
uh yeah, scor game deadline which is
like a toa defender. Packed which is
like a mobile jewel stuff. Uh,
Starlight, it's like a not Space
Invader. It's a arcad uh game stuff like
a
plane when you shoot and then you move
and stuff like that.
>> Uh, Red Line, which is um it's like a
Sonic alternative
edge dog. You just run across the map
and because you have a messenger to
deliver blah blah.
>> Uh, Ro, I don't remember this one.
Uh the platform. Oh yeah. No, it's um
Super Mario.
>> Oh, cool.
>> So yeah, I I want to I want to try
different game style and see which one
is like the easier to um to implement.
And the war line is table commander/maps
and it's a hobby for because it will be
all of that will be multiplayer because
why not? And uh it's a map with the wall
and stuff.
>> Yeah. And that's why you make it more
difficult, right? Because a multiplayer
is not just a one-shotted game that runs
locally.
>> Yeah. I mean, you know, like uh I I
define a scope and then oh, I have no
idea. Let's promp that. Let's see where
it goes. Uh so play no dead road. That's
the game. And obviously everything is
open source. So if you want to check how
we did that, uh check all of the links,
the skills, uh the games itself, all of
the repository, everything is uh free
and it's also based on the skills that
we have and like the ship sheet dev vo
template, everything is a monor repo. So
everything is accessible and public and
if you want to pay us, you can buy a
studio pass for $99 $99 a month.
>> Yeah, you're lucky. Only $29.
>> Yes, exactly. And yeah, also clean clean
uh clean clean content because uh we can
uh the bit lock and the asset gallery
all all of the stuff. So yeah, not
everything is clean but uh yeah like so
everything has been generated by uh
collects. So see like for example those
assets uh that's not clean like the
purple it should not be here and here
it's bleeding here. So yeah, it's just a
draft for now,
>> but uh it's getting there because uh Oh,
that's the previous version. Before it
was pixelized art. Uh t tech tag. Yeah,
all of that it's all draft. Um tech tag
tech tag tech. That's some sick design.
>> Yeah, I did a good job.
>> Yeah,
that's the first weapon we played. Uh we
played with it. We play with uh bridge
boss. Okay, cool. So,
uh, now the second website is Dead Rot,
which is the game by itself. And I'm
going to the same thing like with the
law and stuff. I'm going to talk about
the law, too, because uh that's going to
be interesting. But first demo of the
game. So, we are going into the war
lane. It's gonna be uh loud because
that's a doom like uh design uh mood.
But uh yeah, so reduce the sounds
back. Enter the
a little bit.
That's better.
in your head.
So we have okay
lot because I can't speak over
uh resume. So we have a comments table
where it's going to be a strategy based
uh stuff with like resources that will
impact all of those games
return
uh like I'm going to show you the FPS
first because that's the most uh uh
builtin uh game. So, sketch survivor
player run. You can choose your uh
character. There is different weapons.
Uh again, a shotgun, SMG, and um a
sniper. I'm going to uh try with the
shotgun. That would be funnier. And now
we are back on the map.
Oh,
they explode. There is blood. There is
like some um uh
members and stuff and that's the bonus.
So, you're improving your um
your
>> Yes. So, yeah, your abilities.
>> Yes, exactly. Abilities during the game
then
I'm going to just Oh.
Oh, game crashed.
>> You You broke it.
>> Broke it.
>> It probably needed to restart because of
the the different settings.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that should not happen. But
yeah. Okay, that's a bug. Maybe Fable
Fight can fix that. Uh T player run. I'm
going to try with another one. So now we
have another weapon and it's SMG.
But okay, that that's the game.
Okay. Uh, I'm going to back to the I'm
going to go back to the lobby.
>> Uh, okay. So, stablat that the plane
game.
You're going to see it right away. So,
I'm a plane and then there's like some
space invaders coming like and I'm
shooting them.
And same thing like same gaming loop.
You have abilities and you get you
improve them.
That That's it. That's the game. I'm I'm
wondering if I should like do it like a
3D, but I'm curious about the sprites
that have
>> that makes it difficult.
>> Yeah.
Main menu path more lane
path. Uh okay. So, Starlight, we did it.
Uh packful.
Yeah. See, like for example, like the
sprite is bleeding on the right and
because it's one band and it should only
display the one image.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Uh that's the mobile. Okay. That was one
prompt of Opus
4.8 that's supposed to be like a League
of Legend, but we're not here yet.
>> It need It needs some modifications.
Uh attack uh one n I don't even have the
full menu yet. So attack dead lane.
Okay, I can I can jump over the table.
Attack path deploy. Oh yeah, that's the
to defender. It's sick. So I'm building
a a tower.
>> Mhm.
>> And then a defense game.
>> Yes.
And and the first prompt was like a 3D
views.
>> The game works. [__] works.
And I can I have gold, so I can rebuild
the tower again.
>> Mhm.
>> Build more.
It's going to be I I think this one is
going to be It's going to be amazing.
Okay, that's it.
>> This is cool.
>> Yeah, it's nice. T
uh co survival. We did it. and Roform.
Yeah, that's the
Super Mario. Yes. So, I'm going right
puff puff. And no, it's going to It
crashed.
>> Oh,
>> yeah. It crashed.
>> Check that you don't fall into the lava.
>> Yeah, I can't go over that for some
reason.
>> Invisible wall.
>> So, tech. And uh where is the Sonic? Oh
[__]
Where is the Sonic game? Uh, I did that.
Warhog, I did that. Blightful.
Dead lane. Huh?
I didn't do dead lane. No, dead lane is
the Yes. Did I miss the game?
>> Is it behind you?
>> That was it.
>> Yes. Okay. So, that's the Sonic game.
>> That's like hyperactive. Yeah, but I
think like the core loop and the core
mechanics needs to be uh that it's going
to be like super fast and stuff
>> and it's buggy as hell. Like all of the
collision stuff, it's not Yeah. And
that's it. That's the game. You cross
the line, you finish the line, you put
the messenger, blah blah blah, and then
that's it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And you just want to improve
your time.
>> Exactly. Uh so yes. Cool.
That's the basics. Now, what we can do
is to build the tools to uh generate all
of the assets and all for all of those
games to make them better. Uh oh. Um I
can Okay, I I think we should use like
replicate and nano banana pro.
>> I didn't set up that. Oh [__] Uh I
forgot to take the keys. Um, so
yes,
uh, yes, I want that. I want that.
And now I want replace
load path. So now I'm going I went back
to code because it's going to be more
visible than the CLI. And I work quickly
on Yes. Okay. The map picker. Instead of
changing the map in the scorch game, now
we can have a picker like a map picker
in the
uh just after you select the player.
>> Mhm.
>> I think that's it. Check out what
actually been inviting. Okay. Pick the
Ply with tree. Okay. Proceed. You zero
download ever. What?
run play in first which cash
the only download after play right. Oh
okay.
If you really want zero download ever is
the play config. So test run against you
install ah test run depend on whatever
chrome version.
Uh
so
uh
uh we good or not?
>> Most important question for every AI.
>> Uh do
do I need to do do anything
buff?
>> Oh, did you fix everything?
>> Yeah, fixed everything. God damn it.
>> Yeah. And if not, go into loop. Did you
fix it? No. Fix it.
>> Fix. Okay.
Uh, close as completed. Move to done.
Consume ship sheet engine. Yes. Three
game already depends on it. World bounce
camera rig. Uh, commented with audit
findings, projectile combat, earth
score. Yes. Okay. Adapt adaptive music.
Yes. Because the music should be based
even on the action of the game that you
have. you it should like u change.
>> Mhm.
>> Asset ring one of seven games down. Yes.
Okay. So that's the FPS. So yeah, we
don't have any assets for all of the
other games. Weapon ti. So yeah, in the
score survivor,
>> the more point you have it will visually
enhance your weapons. And I even like
for the guns, I want like two weapons
because uh if if you just have a guns,
you need you need to
to be more fun and more brutal.
Uh yeah. What do you think? Like is that
a good start? Like do you have any
feedback?
>> No, I think this is a good start.
We need to start somewhere and see how
it goes.
>> Yeah. Uh we're good. Oh, see we Yes,
we're good. Let's go.
>> Okay. There's nothing you need to do on
your machine. The browser installed uh
is done once the globally and the sh
Okay.
Okay. Okay. Cool. Uh it's green. Okay.
Uh back
path noise.
Uh the Yeah. Well, okay. Cool. Nice. Uh
okay. So that road and so if we want to
build the tools, it should be in the
ship ship game. um
repo and I want uh yeah also I have the
routines where I like I explained like
every four hours it pick features from
GitHub
>> and it build it and then it and then I I
should add another uh daily GitHub
review where it review all of the PR mer
to master and everything.
>> Mhm. which is basically everything that
needs to be automated. It's basically
include/codex because you have the same
UI in in codex. So when we're going to
have like 5.6 or six GP6 that's going to
be that's going to be lit.
Um oh yeah because all of the asset has
been generated directly via the uh image
gen in codeex which use um
GPT image too
because they have a genative model and
for the voice for the sound. So for the
voice there is no voice yet but uh 11
Labs has a crazy good uh CLI where I can
just uh prompt form code and generate
the sound that I have like the sound
effect or the shotgun or whatever from
11 Labs and it's free like I have like
credits every month so I can even
generate that for free.
>> Oh that's cool.
>> And for Sunu there is daily credits
where I can uh generate music like like
the one we have for free every day.
They're giving up free credit.
>> Yeah. Well, I would say just keep using
it.
>> Yeah. Free. Well, yeah. I'm not I'm not
spending money on music.
>> No.
>> Um, okay. So, bomb the board. Oh, I
didn't. Ah,
>> what did we forget?
And what model do you have right now?
>> Ah, I see it at the bottom right. Table
five and low. five low and auto for
because I want to auto everything.
>> Yes,
>> because uh it's smart. It's smart smart.
Um so that is the law which is
um
ship games
like I'm gonna start with that event uh
path. So the public repository are
shipping games dead rot and the skills
and everything is a monor repo which for
dead rot um we have all of the games in
app/ games but we have the law which is
an obsidian vault with only markdown
files
and I can uh so what I do is uh I write
the law
>> like the story etc.
And then all of the games are attached
to the law.
>> Yeah. So everything is connected and
>> everything is consistent and everything
would uh give us uh consist.
Okay. Nice.
Okay.
>> Yeah. So that means that every game is
playing in the same world.
>> Exactly. That's the same universe. And
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. So that's awesome. Oh, every time
every time I speak, I can hear
something. Do you?
>> Yeah, I think they were downstairs with
drilling again.
>> Yes, but no, that's me speaking. Wait,
>> this one?
>> Better. No.
>> Best.
>> Is that new or is that just now?
>> No. No. It just started.
better. Oh
>> yeah, this sounds good.
>> Okay, it's my connection of the mic.
Damn, that's sad. Damn.
>> Have Fable fix it.
>> Uh that's that's hardware, bro.
>> Maybe he will just order an engineer.
>> Um yeah, I mean we need the AI robot to
ch to fix hardware now.
>> Oh yeah.
Uh, okay. So,
um, yeah, the Obsidian Vault. So, yeah,
every like the design I have like the
design MD file that will be consistent
with everything, all of the games, all
of the universe is based on that. Uh, I
will probably like change it along the
way, but uh, like everything and because
it's a monor repo, then the agent has
the context of that all the time. Mhm.
>> And I it should at least refer to it all
the time.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And get almost the same
styling and
>> Exactly.
>> And then I can always like Yeah. Go go
go back to refer yourself to uh the uh
the vault check. Yeah. Like the game
what we defined for the game problem low
the gold you want format win condition
like it's just nuts. And then you
iterate on top of that again and again
and again for weeks, months, and then
you have a
cool Mario Party Doom like game.
>> Yeah.
So yeah. Uh I don't have an
Okay, I have a look. Okay, nice art from
batch. No, nice nice.
That's sick. I just I asked it to attach
the Oh, nice.
>> So, yeah, I can also use that for the
consistency of all of the art stuff that
leads.
>> No characters was locked yet. The
scourge many host and bridge boss are
the only promot promoted locked.
>> Why can you It's happening again, right?
That one
>> better.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. That was the plastic on my Okay.
Nice. Cool. Fixed. No need for AI.
>> No. Yeah. Well, sometimes we can do
stuff ourselves.
>> Yeah.
But really, sometimes, bro, like not all
the time.
>> No, not all the time. But we can try.
>> Yeah. Uh, okay. So, back here. Back.
Gold. I'm going to replace that. Replace
character path. Uh, no, I want load path
path. Uh, cool. Oh, m picker. Matt
picker. Produce local run produce
specific react.com. Nice, nice, nice,
nice, nice. Yeah, like I I love all of
those skills and all of those uh uh
plugins like a React Doctor to just scan
on CI and because it's an open source
project, we run it for free on GitHub.
Love that.
>> Okay. So, uh I don't we don't have any
app. I don't uh in the ship [__] ship
[__] games.
Oh, we do. Nice. We do have an app. So
I'm going to run it
uh include directly
um
like run the apps apps in preview
so I can see what we have right now.
stuff rename apps
app.
It's already like a 40 minutes 45.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. We're gonna we're
gonna ship a small features then.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Let's show something.
>> Yeah. Um
I think what I
what I would like to have is
a proper sprite generator.
Uh, open dash. Oh,
nice. Oh, yeah. So, that's what people
will have once the they pay us the 20
bucks a month.
>> 29 bucks. Get the pass link to ship was
blocked. Okay. Sign in. Yeah. Nice. Uh,
oh, I I did not have the keys. Okay.
Dashboard. Sign in. Okay. Everything is
on click.
Okay. Cool. Awesome. Uh, awesome.
Can you give me a quick features that we
can demo uh quickly with the uh app?
Uh,
maybe one to generate uh assets for the
games with the replicate integration
for the game. the replicate
integration uh to generate
right
with nano
uh nano banana.
Okay. So why I'm doing that? I want to
uh get the keys from clerk.
>> Mhm.
>> So dashboard
cl because I'm kind of forgot about it.
Cl
login.
It takes some time.
Fable is spending a lot of tokens right
now.
Ah, you're muted or your mic broke.
Yeah.
I think it's broken.
Oh, he's out of batteries.
That's the same issue.
Is it better?
>> Yeah, this is better.
>> Okay.
Uh oh,
>> you out of batteries.
>> Yeah. No, I think it's
uh input.
>> Yeah.
>> Is it better?
>> Yeah. Yeah, this is better.
>> Okay.
Uh no, I can hear it again.
Oh, maybe not.
>> Yeah, it looks like you have a broken
wire or something or loose connection.
Okay. Because I connected directly to
the roadboard, but Okay. I'm going to
check like quickly the state of the song
before that.
>> Mhm.
Okay. No, it works.
>> It works. Yes.
>> Off. Okay. Cool. Uh, drop replicate. I'm
not doing that live.
Uh, attack. Okay. Okay. So, what I want
is to set up that. Nope. Not this thing.
I want to copy that. Nope. I want that.
Copy. I want that. And I want It said
replicate API token. Replicate
API
token. That's what I forgot to for
add generic password. What?
What? What is it ask? What is it doing?
I refine the full flow for the preview
the page render and click generate
correctly. It's the API. Uh the error
you see on the screen shows no replic
generation security. Wait, what? Why?
Why?
Why is that setting up the replicate?
Oh, I said oh. Oh, I'm on the page.
>> Yes.
>> Nice.
Okay, cool. Uh, so I just need the key
replicate
back. Replicate. Run.
Sign in.
Sign in with GitHub. We're getting
there. We're getting there. We're
getting there.
Uh, what? Login, bro. Why is it not
working? Gab.
Okay.
What? Unable to sign up.
Look.
Replace.
Nope. Nope. Uh. Oh.
What the heck?
Wait.
What
is it? Broken.
44 replicate. What the heck?
Oh, is it GitHub?
What? Okay, cool. We're in uh ship ship
dev. Yes, I'm going to So, I'm not going
to share that
>> like to replace replace
load
uh load. Oh, no. I'm in I'm on my Okay.
load path. Uh I was on the
uh cursor page. Cool. So I have money on
my It's happening again.
>> Yes.
And it killed your voice.
test.
>> Yes, this is better.
>> I need a new mic.
>> Yeah.
>> Um,
so ship [__] games
great token.
Uh puff
puff buff puff
uh attack. And now we can reload. Load.
Okay, that's annoying. Attack. I think
it's good. Nice. Write description. An
undead pirate captain with a Okay.
Andron pixel art low poly dity
H. Okay. Um, so is everything
in
place? Oh,
don't check F.
>> Yeah. F keys.
>> And then it says this wasn't in your
environment file.
>> Uh, okay. Um,
imagine a scourge from deadro.com.
Okay. Dead rod. Dead rot. Dead rot.
Is that going to be no banana? Is that
going to generate right away?
There's no no echoing anywhere. Bum bum
bum. Nice.
And sometimes you see like uh cloud is
continuing a lot of seconds and not
using tokens. Is that when we stand in
line waiting for other people?
>> Uh so for me it's uh it's when it's
processing code.
>> Ah yeah
>> right.
>> Uh and that's it. That works.
>> That's cool.
>> Nice. Okay. So, uh, path.
So, what I want, uh, I need those assets
to be related to the game I want to
generate the sprite for.
>> Mhm.
>> So, how can we do that? Oh, sorry. I was
prompting with a whisper
to be related to the game. I want to
generate the sprite for. How can we do
that? B, the demo flow is simple. Open
asset type of sprite description Peter
statip generate and the result land in
the grid. Uh 24 that's amazing.
Um,
also I want a gallery of all of the
asset we have generated and I want to
regenerate the asset uh if we uh want to
reprint it differently
and if we need to generate them u
with different sprite and position.
Okay. Back.
Uh, okay. Andron 2D
back
locally dark greeting. Oh, okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. That's That's
okay. So, in my
uh
nice Okay, cool. Uh dashboard. Oh, yes.
Yeah. And I know banana. Okay. 10
seconds. And it cost me
7 cents.
>> That's not too bad.
>> Yeah. Seven cents to generate one image.
Uh handdrawn game sprite of imaging.
Yeah. Okay. Okay. So yeah, we need to
work on that. We need to work on the
pro. We need to work like the input. I
can also have an input of the image. So
yeah, that's the
that's the two. Okay, so like there's
absolutely nothing like the design of
dead rot stuff, but hopefully it will
pick it up now. Puff path path
path cl
um I want to be able to uh generate
batches of images. I think with Nano
Banana uh 2 we can have different
output. So add that in the prompt. Also
use the skill to prompt the asset and to
keep the consistency in it. Um because
it should be from the game we want to
select to prompt for.
Also explain to me which kind of sprite
we are going to need if we want to add
those sprites into the games and what's
the workflow for the next um asset
management
for the integration to the game
directly.
Oh no
[__] Uh game we want to pronto uh do I
have a gall? No. Okay. What I say accept
uh I want to be able to gen B of image
also use
X a swarm reaper enemy locking forward
uh those prompt or [__]
dead lane. Ah my mic
I am hearing you.
Oh not anymore.
What about now?
>> No. Yes.
>> Okay. It's 100% like the connection
between the mic and the extender. I
don't know if Okay. Wait.
Is it better now? Oh, okay. Let's see.
Okay, so uh BR skill to prompt assets.
Bam. Bam. Okay, we're going to start it.
So, I want to gallery generated. I want
to generate the assets. I want to
reprint it. Okay. French accent. Mhm.
Need to generate in different sprite and
position. Okay. What is it going to
think about that?
Bam. Bam. Bam. I I like I like AI
generation.
I mean, I can't do that with this
generation the with this generated
assets because like the small flies
needs to be out.
>> Mhm.
>> But uh
that's sick.
I love it. Oh, is that generated? Uh is
that saved locally?
page API assets generate list file. No,
I don't I don't have the
where where where are the Oh, is it
displaying directly from
uh
from replicate probably.
Okay. Matt picker. Matt picker.
P
final state all 20 doc okay skip same as
before react doctor check itself fast
and the B summary table yes so like with
those like pipeline on CI
>> then we have like recursive like not
recursive but uh fully automated test
testing so
>> it should improve the quality of the
software shipped because then you have
CI and QA quad drills
I love that.
Oh, style. Nice. Ideal attacking,
running, jumping, side views.
Yes. Okay. Uh, type check pass.
Is that Oh, it's not even ultra code.
Did I Did I pass that or is it one
script then reprint it in different? Um,
because yeah, I like ultra ultra code is
really really nice. Can I still Can I
use that somewhere? I don't think so.
Oh, reprint. I
>> Let's see.
>> I love AI. So cool.
>> It's so easy. You say what you wonder,
you get it.
>> I don't. Do you have more bugs when you
start a project from scratch with AI
than having
something like a codebase that is uh you
add a AI uh layer on top of it slash
code on top of that.
>> Yeah, you need to have AI do an
inventoriization of of all the rules,
the code, the framework, then you don't
get any bugs. But if you say, "Hey, this
is the system. go create this,
>> you're getting a lot of bugs because it
just focuses on that step and doesn't
read everything else in the framework.
>> Yeah, 100%.
>> And yeah,
>> if you're building it yourself after
every step and every documentation, you
say uh write this to the documentation
or update the documentation. Yeah, I
mean uh yeah, like I have a session
s
I have a session end skill that you can
find in like the ship ship skill uh key
zero stuff v0 no ship ship dev/sklls
>> which document everything inside agents
sessions. So I have the history of all
of the sessions and the agent can should
read that every time we have um a proper
uh like at the end of the session and
documentation to get back to it and
track it. But also I use GitHub as a
source of truth.
Like my GitHub is like yeah I I've
connected all of the project to GitHub
and I want all of the project to have
specs to uh to then like ask the AI
agent to get back to it.
>> Mhm. So yeah uh and in term of usage uh
like the session was restarted when um
just before we went live and okay 15 70%
that's nice.
Okay preview preview I love that it's
lit
page. So yeah, I have the reprint.
Uh, wait, it's
running.
Wait, that's Oh, that's Oh, that's the
mob running and that's the mob
attacking. Yeah, doesn't I can't use
that.
>> It doesn't look alike.
>> Yeah. No, it doesn't look like the same
thing.
>> And then it loses a lot of stuff.
>> Um, okay. So what I do is that gallery
no path
path tech
path
all of those assets are not consistent.
So when I ask for a reprint you need to
use the origin of the image
the original image. Yeah, I think we
have a reprint that tries to do
something similar but create a new
version.
>> Yeah, exactly. Yeah, there is no input
in the in the image input in the in the
prompt. Um, reprint, you need to use
original image. Add a loader
in the grid when an image is generated.
and buff.
Cool, cool, cool.
Nice.
Okay, so what are you doing, bro?
Yeah. Um, I didn't check the token per
second.
>> Mhm.
>> It's kind of slow, no onload versus uh
codeex. No.
>> Yeah, it's slower. Yeah.
So yeah, you you prompt like five
session and then you go away and you
come back and then poof, you have a
billion dollar company image.
>> But you just work in in multiple uh
windows so that's no problem.
>> Yeah. With like ghosty like 16 image and
stuff.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh but yeah, long uh Okay, maybe we can
uh we can pause there because Yeah, it's
going to cook. Um,
I think I think we can continue. Oh,
wait, wait, wait. Uh, it's all works.
The gar no hold the swam reaper violent
for scourge survival in different pose
attacking running each tag in with its
game and pose and each card has it own
post speaker plus a post speaker. Yeah.
Pixel art attacking
form reaper enemy. Yeah. Okay. Okay.
Okay. So I can
uh I can select reprints and okay
generate the uh
fire is reprint button persistent lab
store saved every render to a gig no
asset labs I have it
app
uh
said I don't see I don't see it
I said lapstone what
okay whatever oh no I don't see it okay
I will look into it later um
load
where is it
load uh gallery the page load everything
from API list on mood new reprint with
variation cool the generated form also
gain a post selector attacking side
views and API. Oh, it's because Oh,
okay. Okay. So, I can select the style
the prompt from here and Okay. One cave
for the demo. Poses are fresh generation
containing on the same prompts. So, the
creator design drift between poses. You
can see the four ribs different. Yeah.
If you want consistent character sheets,
the next step will be filling the
original image. No [__] bro. Let me
check the repo. Found it. General at BR.
Perfect. Uh, and give me a consistent
uh
one by four sprite
with poses
of the same characters
and then okay after that we could
uh
we we're going to stop it but okay. So
build prompt game style looks like it.
Okay. Uh I al I want to code
uh to
describe the
go in the prompt that will help
consistency
consistency between the uh rights
gapers
build a help her to not gate but bath.
Let's go. I'm hyped.
But yeah, and everything will be open
source and then and then we build a
studio and then
>> and then we have the most perfect game
ever.
>> Uh yeah, we have GTA 6.
>> But but the cool thing is if people use
this, they can change some settings and
they can create it for a totally
different game. Everything unique.
>> Exactly. And Okay. So I don't want to
lick the air but uh tag
tag tag uh path replace
share
uh no that's the game the other one
play oh I'm going to
uh asset labs yes cool so here the
architecture of the repo is like pretty
straightforward where
um okay so you have all of the assets
etc but um
we have packages
oh maybe it's here
um yeah so everything is extracted to
build for that uh games uh in the ship
sheet uh game stuff but like the engine
to build all of the sprite or like to
animate the monster in the game can
works in other game and like you said
yeah if people wants to um
uh use that CLI or those integration etc
they can to generate their own sprite
>> and uh for their own uh stuff
>> yeah it's a good start you can use it as
basis
>> exactly and um I also have like
resources which is uh some YouTube
channel that I've uh
dropped the YouTube link and it extract
the transcript.
>> Mhm.
>> And by doing that I have everything that
I talk about.
>> Mhm.
>> And if there is any rules that I need to
know to build the games then I can drop
it and uh read the transcript and create
the next tool on stuff like that.
It's cool. Yeah. And shout out to AI
oriented dev. like I love his channel.
It's it's uh it's going to be us later
on. But I I already show you that,
right?
>> Yeah, he is giving a good example.
>> Uh
where is he?
AI AI oriented game.
Yes. Back path puff replace.
I love his channel. Like it's really
cool. Uh and he's making making a lot of
views like his uh V Fighter games.
Amazing.
Oh.
>> Yeah. Commercials.
>> Yeah. I don't I don't have it was not
the right brother for the right profile.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Look. Look at this. This is good. This
is nuts.
This is awesome quality.
>> Yeah.
>> Like it's it's like it's frame perfect.
It's It's awesome.
And it did that like crazy
with the same tools that we have.
>> Mhm. And one uh technique that I learned
from his transcript is to uh for example
for an animation instead of generate
sprites from image to image you generate
a video and then you extract the frame
of the animation.
>> Then it's always the exact same styling.
>> Exactly. And it's not bleeding from one
to another. Uh just going to be a bit
more expensive um uh to generate. So
yeah, that's a problem. Uh
Oh, what's up, Grim? Oh, sorry. Missed
your com. Yeah, the same as a fiber
video game is making searching a
nightmare. Yeah, for real.
That's that's a problem for sure. Uh,
and okay, sprite terrific. I mean, you
can drop the tools that they they use
and drop it to fable and uh to like copy
paste and v coding the same process
stuff.
I love it.
Uh tag. Okay, so load.
Okay, now we're talking.
Replace
uh load path path.
Look. Nice.
>> We're going good way.
>> Nice.
>> Now you just need to be able to split
it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But then like it's just
Yeah, that's that's lit. But okay, see
that for example, it should never do
that because it's out of frame.
>> So that should not happen.
>> Yeah, but you have good results. No,
it's just optimizing.
>> Exactly.
Like
uh download of
download. Where is it? What?
Wait,
I have one PNG. Oh, okay.
Like back replace
window
preview. Where is my preview? What? I
don't have preview. Oh,
because I spaced it. I didn't click on
it. That's my bed.
Review bath
>> noise. Okay. So, it's not the same. Uh,
>> it looks almost the same.
>> Yeah,
>> almost.
>> I mean, yeah, like the scale is not the
same.
But yeah, basically like it should rep
like reprompt it with um I mean you can
even like just cut that and you nobody
will see the difference, right? Cuz it's
still pixel. But yeah, other than that
>> it has some like sometimes it has four
pipes on his shoulder plate, a lot of
time three, but
>> it's getting in the correct direction.
>> Yes. Okay, man. I think we can slowly
wrap it up. Do you have anything like to
uh address
right now? This looks good.
>> Yeah, I already have a sprite directive.
Sprite prom directive. Let me check.
Nice, nice, nice. Love it. Love it.
>> Let it go and see what it does.
>> Yes. Should we do like a series of live
video about how to how we progress with
that?
>> Oh yeah, that's cool.
>> Yeah, like it or
>> even just small followup but just let's
go uh and see let people see what we are
doing next. Exactly. Exactly. And
hopefully uh have some revenue because
people will buy the uh
>> the awesome skills
>> subscription.
>> Yeah, we need to work on that offer when
once we have a finished product. But
yeah, okay, that's a conversation for
another stream.
>> Perfect. So, thanks a lot
>> and yeah, everyone subscribe to the
channel. Thanks for watching the video.
Um.